Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files K-O, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files M
    - Millard, Charles E. F. (Box A-84, Folder 168)
      One print has photocopied leaf press release attached.
    - Millard, William (Det.) (Box A-84, Folder 169)
    - Millard, William (Box A-84, Folder 170)
    - Millberry, Gene (Box A-84, Folder 171)
    - Millen, Barbara (Miss) (Box A-84, Folder 172)
    - Millender, Mallory (Box A-84, Folder 173)
      Print has single-leaf press release attached with staple on border.
    - Miller, Albert L. (Box A-84, Folder 174)
    - Miller, Albert (Box A-84, Folder 175)
      Photographer if identified: Toogood's
    - Monet Miller, Alexandria (Box A-84, Folder 176)
    - Miller, Alice (Box A-84, Folder 177)
    - Miller, Ann (Box A-84, Folder 178)
    - Miller, Arthur (Box A-84, Folder 179)
      Note on folder: "Slained by policeman in Brooklyn." Also three newspaper article clippings. Three prints are stuck together.
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photo, Dave Greene
    - Miller, Arthur (Box A-84, Folder 180)
    - Miller, Augustus (Mrs.) (Box A-84, Folder 181)
    - Miller, Bebe (Box A-84, Folder 182)
      Print has computer-printed typescript press release attached on verso.
    - Miller, Betti Jean (Box A-84, Folder 183)
    - Miller Brewing Co. (Box A-84, Folder 184)
      One print has computer-printed typescript press release (two leaves) attached with paperclip; one has single computer-printed typescript leaf press release attached with paperclip.
    - Miller, C. (Box A-84, Folder 185)
    - Miller. C. Leonard (Box A-84, Folder 186)
    - Miller, Charles (Box A-84, Folder 187)
    - Miller, Charles H. (Box A-84, Folder 188)
      Photographer if identified: Pach Bros. N.Y.
    - Miller, Clyde H., Jr. (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 189)
    - Miller, Cornelia (Box A-84, Folder 190)
    - Miller, Dahlia H. (Jr.) (Box A-84, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: Studio 5
    - Miller, Damon (Box A-84, Folder 192)
    - Miller, David (Box A-84, Folder 193)
    - Miller, Diane (Miss) (Box A-84, Folder 194)
      One print has single typescript leaf description adhered on verso.
    - Miller, Debbie (Box A-84, Folder 195)
      Photographer if identified: Ron Brown
    - Miller, Donald L. (Box A-84, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Army Photographer, Pictorial Enterprise, Studio of The New York Times
    - Miller, Donald (Captain + Mrs.) (Box A-84, Folder 197)
    - Miller, Dorie (Box A-84, Folder 198)
    - Miller, Douglas (Box A-84, Folder 199)
    - Miller, Earl L. (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-84, Folder 200)
    - Miller, Ed (Box A-84, Folder 201)
    - Miller, Edith (Judge) (Box A-84, Folder 202)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Dick De Marsico, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Miller, Evelyn B. (Box A-84, Folder 203)
      Also two velox prints. One print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Bro. David McAdams, Paul Parker, Ted Davis
    - Miller, Frank (Box A-84, Folder 204)
    - Miler, Frederick E. (Box A-84, Folder 205)
      Photographer if identified: Savoy Studios
    - Miller, George (Box A-84, Folder 206)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert/News Voice International, Bill Price
    - Miller, Gordon (Box A-84, Folder 207)
    - Miller, Harold G. (Box A-84, Folder 208)
    - Miller, Helen (Box A-84, Folder 209)
      One print is mounted on cardstock.
      Photographer if identified: Hawkins Studio, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Miller, J. Irwin (Box A-84, Folder 210)
    - Miller, J. C. (Box A-84, Folder 211)
      Also one single-leaf press release.
    - Miller, Jacqueline W. (Box A-84, Folder 212)
    - Miller, James B. (Box A-84, Folder 213)
    - Miller, James (Box A-84, Folder 214)
    - Miller, James (Snake) (Box A-84, Folder 215)
    - Miller, Jean (Box A-84, Folder 216)
    - Miller, Jimmy (Box A-84, Folder 217)
    - Miller, Joan (Box A-84, Folder 218)
    - Miller, John (Box A-84, Folder 219)
    - Miller, John III (Box A-84, Folder 220)
      Photographer if identified: Albert J. Robbins
    - Miller, John (Box A-84, Folder 221)
    - Miller, John H. (Box A-84, Folder 222)
      Photographer if identified: Ralph Saunders
    - Miller, John N. (Box A-84, Folder 223)
    - Miller, Johnny (Box A-84, Folder 224)
    - Miller, Joseph (Elder) (Box A-84, Folder 225)
    - Miller, Joyce (Box A-84, Folder 226)
    - Miller, Julia (Dr.) (Box A-84, Folder 227)
      Photographer if identified: Bohannon Portrait Studio
    - Miller, Julius (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 228)
    - Miller, Kid "Punch" (Box A-84, Folder 229)
    - Miller, Lamar (Dr.) (Box A-84, Folder 230)
    - Miller, Larry (Box A-84, Folder 231)
      Photographer if identified: New York City Housing Authority
    - Miller, Lawrence (Box A-84, Folder 232)
    - Miller, Leonard L. (Box A-84, Folder 233)
    - Miller, Leroy (Box A-84, Folder 234)
    - Miller, Levette (Box A-84, Folder 235)
    - Miller, Levi B. (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 236)
    - Miller, Linda (Box A-84, Folder 237)
    - Miller, Lionel (Box A-84, Folder 238)
    - Miller, Lois (Box A-84, Folder 239)
    - Miller, Loren (Box A-84, Folder 240)
    - Miller, Lynette (Box A-84, Folder 241)
    - Mille, Mae (Box A-84, Folder 242)
    - Miller, Mary (Mrs.) (Box A-84, Folder 243)
    - Miller, Mary Catherine (Box A-84, Folder 244)
      Photographer if identified: Keno-Foto Service
    - Miller, Melville "Doc" (Box A-84, Folder 245)
    - Miller, Norma (Box A-84, Folder 246)
    - Miller, Oliver O. (Box A-84, Folder 247)
    - Miller, Reynold (Box A-84, Folder 248)
    - Miller, Robert Anthony (Box A-84, Folder 249)
    - Miller, Robert R. C. (Box A-84, Folder 250)
    - Miller, Ron (Box A-84, Folder 251)
    - Miller, Roosevelt Stan (Box A-84, Folder 252)
      Photographer if identified: Matar Studio
    - Miller, Rosalind S. (Mrs.) (Box A-84, Folder 253)
    - Miller, Ross (Dr.) (Box A-84, Folder 254)
      One print has photocopied press release (two leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Miller, Roy (Box A-84, Folder 255)
    - Miller, Sheryl (Box A-84, Folder 256)
    - Miller Sisters (Group) (Box A-84, Folder 257)
    - Miller, Stephanie (Box A-84, Folder 258)
    - Miller, Herbert, Jr. (Box A-84, Folder 259)
    - Miller, Taft (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 260)
    - Miller, Ted (Box A-84, Folder 261)
    - Miller, W. B. (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 262)
    - Miller's Show Place, Frank (Box A-84, Folder 263)
    - Millett, Duane Aaron (Box A-84, Folder 264)
    - Millett, Eileen Daphne (Box A-84, Folder 265)
    - Miller, Samuel D. (Box A-84, Folder 266)
    - Miller, George W. (Box A-84, Folder 267)
      Also five velox prints and one single-leaf typescript letter. One print is mounted on board; one is cut out and mounted on paper.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Ralph Cooper, Newell Johnson, Wide World Photos, David McAdams, Sherm Scott, Camera Associates
      Number of Prints: 31
    - Millett, Duane Aaron (Box A-84, Folder 268)
    - Millett, Eileen Daphne (Box A-84, Folder 269)
    - Millhouse, Bertrand (Box A-84, Folder 270)
      One print has three images; one has four images. Three prints have single carbonscript leaf press releases attached on verso with staples on border.
    - Millette, Robert (Prof.) (Box A-84, Folder 271)
    - Milligan, Robie (Box A-84, Folder 272)
    - Millinder, Lucky (Box A-84, Folder 273)
      Photographer if identified: Al Ben-Ness, Platnick Photos, David McAdams
    - Millionaires, The (Box A-84, Folder 274)
    - Milligan, Joseph (Box A-84, Folder 275)
    - Miligan, Michael L. (Box A-84, Folder 276)
    - Mills, Alfred (Box A-84, Folder 277)
      Note on folder: "See Harold Richardson."
    - Mills, Alvin (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 278)
    - Mills House, Alfred (Box A-84, Folder 279)
    - Mills, Alfred S. (Box A-84, Folder 280)
      Note on folder: "See Urias Wilson."
    - Mills, Alvin L. (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 281)
    - Mills, B. E. (Box A-84, Folder 282)
    - Mills Brothers (Group) (Box A-84, Folder 283)
    - Mills, Bryant (Box A-84, Folder 284)
    - Mills, Cedric E. Rt. (Rev.) (Box A-84, Folder 285)
      Photographer if identified: Spear
    - Mills, Curtis (Box A-84, Folder 286)
      Photographer if identified: Camera Associates, Karl Crutchfield
    - Mills, Don (Box A-84, Folder 287)
      Photographer if identified: United Nations, Lloyd Patterson
    - Mills, Duckie (Box A-84, Folder 288)
    - Mills, Eileen (Box A-84, Folder 289)
    - Mills, Elizabeth (Box A-84, Folder 290)
    - Mills, Hughie E. (Box A-84, Folder 291)
    - Mills, Jesse R., Jr. (Box A-84, Folder 292)
      Print has newspaper clipping on verso.
    - Manhattan H. S. of Commerce (Box A-85, Folder 1)
    - Mills, John (Box A-85, Folder 2)
    - Mills, Mary Lee (Box A-85, Folder 3)
    - Mills, Ruth B. (Box A-85, Folder 4)
    - Mills, Stephanie (Box A-85, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Bryan D. Hall, Pictorial Enterprise, Billy Pierce Jr.
    - Mills, Stephanie (Box A-85, Folder 6)
      Two prints are folded in the corner. Also three velox prints. One velox has a caption strip stuck to the recto.
      Photographer if identified: Leonard L. Grand, Peterkin Photo
    - Mills, Stephen L. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-85, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Glamour Pix Photo
    - Mills, William (Box A-85, Folder 8)
    - Milner, John (Box A-85, Folder 9)
    - Milner, Ronald (Box A-85, Folder 10)
      Photographer if identified: Martha Holmes
    - Milner, Thirman (Box A-85, Folder 11)
    - Milo, Makenzie (Box A-85, Folder 12)
      Also one velox print with ms. caption stuck to the verso.
    - Milton, Dennis (Box A-85, Folder 13)
    - Milton, John (Box A-85, Folder 14)
    - Milton, Joseph (Box A-85, Folder 15)
    - Milton, Marshall (Box A-85, Folder 16)
    - Milton, Quinman (Box A-85, Folder 17)
      Note on folder: "Also here is Russell Milton."
      Photographer if identified: Glamour Studio
    - Milton, Sharon (Box A-85, Folder 18)
    - Mimford, Thad (Box A-85, Folder 19)
    - Mimieux, Yvette (Box A-85, Folder 20)
    - Mims, Carol (Mrs.) (Box A-85, Folder 21)
      Name on verso of print is "Guy Mills."
    - Mimms, Garnet (Box A-85, Folder 22)
    - Mims, George (Box A-85, Folder 23)
    - Mims, Holly (Box A-85, Folder 24)
    - Mims, Oscar L. (Box A-85, Folder 25)
      Note on folder: "1972." Print is attached to carbonscript leaf by paperclip.
    - Moms, Victor (Box A-85, Folder 26)
      Print has typescript résumé leaf attached to the verso with glue.
    - Mindlin, Robert (Box A-85, Folder 27)
    - Miner, Elias (Rev.) (Box A-85, Folder 28)
      Photographer if identified: Bro David McAdams
    - Ming (Box A-85, Folder 29)
    - Ming, Donald (Rev. & Mrs.) (Box A-85, Folder 30)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes Photography
    - Ming, Edith (Mrs.) (Box A-85, Folder 31)
      Photographer if identified: Baker Photo
    - Ming, William R. (Box A-85, Folder 32)
      One print is stuck to the folder.
    - Mingo, Frank L. (Box A-85, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Monroe S. Frederick II, Jerry Soalt
    - Mingo, Roy E. (Box A-85, Folder 34)
    - Mingo, Sharon (Box A-85, Folder 35)
      Print has three staples in the border.
    - Mingus, Charles (Box A-85, Folder 36)
    - Mini, Junko (Box A-85, Folder 37)
    - Minisink (Box A-85, Folder 38)
      Five print are attached to each other by paperclip. Five prints are cut from larger images. Two pairs of prints are stuck together. One print is attached to one typescript leaf by paperclip. Also one halftone illustration leaf.
      Photographer if identified: Big M Photo Service, Cecil Layne
    - Ministers (Box A-85, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photo, Sharon Freedman, Dave Greene Photo, King Photographers, Luigi
    - Ministers (Box A-85, Folder 40)
      One print has a caption clipped from a newspaper affixed to the verso with tape. One print is torn. One print is attached to one typescript leaf by staple.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, United Press International Photo, L. St. Clair Dummett, Ace Creative Photo, Burt Smith, McAdams Photo, King Photographers
    - Minnelli, Liza (Box A-85, Folder 41)
    - Minner, Prentice (Box A-85, Folder 42)
      One print has the name "George Melville" on the verso. One print is attached to one typescript leaf by staple.
    - Minnis, Wilfred C. (Box A-85, Folder 43)
    - Minnow, Newton (Box A-85, Folder 44)
      Note on folder: "See Dave Hepburn."
    - Minns, Al (Box A-85, Folder 45)
      Note on folder: "See Leon James."
    - Minns, Al, & Sugar Sullivan (Box A-85, Folder 46)
    - Minns, Herb (Box A-85, Folder 47)
    - Minor, Bill (Box A-85, Folder 48)
    - Minor, Bob (Box A-85, Folder 49)
    - Minor, George (Box A-85, Folder 50)
    - Minor, William H. (Box A-85, Folder 51)
      Print has a paperclip affixed to the corner.
    - Minority Biochemical Research Support Program (Box A-85, Folder 52)
    - Minority Business Council Executive Committee (Box A-85, Folder 53)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Ian Anderson
    - Minority Trade Assn. (Box A-85, Folder 54)
    - Minors, Archie (Box A-85, Folder 55)
    - Minott, Ernest R. (Box A-85, Folder 56)
    - Minson, Bill (Box A-85, Folder 57)
    - Minstrel Show (Box A-85, Folder 58)
      One halftone print. Note on folder: "Velox."
    - Minstrels (Box A-85, Folder 59)
    - Minstrels (Box A-85, Folder 60)
      Also one halftone reproduction of two illustrations on a single leaf.
    - Minter, Rae Alexander (Box A-85, Folder 61)
    - Minter, Steve (Box A-85, Folder 62)
    - Minter, Thomas (Box A-85, Folder 63)
      One print is cut in half and the halves are attached to each other by tape. One print has a staple in the border.
    - Minter, William (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-85, Folder 64)
      Photographer if identified: Chuck Smith, Republic Aviation Division Fairchild Hiller Corporation
    - Minton, Russell (Dr.) (Box A-85, Folder 65)
    - Mintz, Bernard (Box A-85, Folder 66)
    - Mintz, Renee (Box A-85, Folder 67)
    - Minyard, Handsel (Box A-85, Folder 68)
    - Miracles (Box A-85, Folder 69)
      Also one typescript leaf. Also one velox print with ms. caption stuck to the verso.
    - Miranda, Lou (Box A-85, Folder 70)
    - Miranda, M. (Box A-85, Folder 71)
    - Miranje, Pamela A. (Box A-85, Folder 72)
    - Miriam Cecelia (Rev. Mother) (Box A-85, Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified prints (Box OS-1, Folder 2, Folder 72)
    - Miss America (Box A-85, Folder 74)
      Print contains seven images.
    - "Miss Truth" (Box A-85, Folder 75)
      Photographer if identified: James Lott
    - Misshore, Joseph O., Jr. (Box A-85, Folder 76)
    - Missing Persons (Box A-85, Folder 77)
      Two prints are Polaroids. One print is attached to one leaf by paperclip. One print has a staple in the border. Also one velox print with caption strip stuck to the recto. Also one photocopied sketch and ms. leaf.
      Photographer if identified: Morris Moritz
    - Mississippi (Box A-85, Folder 78)
      One print has a caption clipped from newspaper attached to the verso with tape.
    - Mississippi - Alabama Southern Releif Committee (Box A-85, Folder 79)
    - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party's (Box A-85, Folder 80)
    - Mississippi Voter Registration (Box A-85, Folder 81)
    - Mister B's (Box A-85, Folder 82)
    - Mr. Rogers (Box A-85, Folder 83)
    - Mr. Wonderful (Box A-85, Folder 84)
    - Mr. World (Box A-85, Folder 85)
    - Mitchell, Alberta (Box A-85, Folder 86)
    - Mitchell, Alvin (Box A-85, Folder 87)
      Photographer if identified: Picot
    - Mitchell, Ann (Miss) (Box A-85, Folder 88)
    - Mitchell, Arthur (Box A-85, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope, Billie Billing, Pictorial Enterprise, Kingsley W. Grant, Fehl
    - Mitchell, Arthur (Box A-85, Folder 90)
      Also one image clipped from newspaper. Also one typescript leaf. One print is cut from a larger image. Also one halftone print.
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope, Kingsley W. Grant, Bob Head, Fehl
    - Mitchell, Arthur (Box A-85, Folder 91)
    - Mitchell, Arthur (Box OS-1, Folder 1)
      Includes quotes from Chaz Illustrated
    - Mitchell, B. Doyle (Box A-85, Folder 92)
      Also two carbonscript leaves attached to each other by two staples and one paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Robert S. Scurlock
    - Mitchell, Ballott (Box A-85, Folder 93)
      Also one velox and caption affixed to paper backing with tape. Name on caption is "Pearlie Ballott Mitchell."
    - Mitchell, Bernice (Box A-85, Folder 94)
    - Mitchell, Bert N. (Box A-85, Folder 95)
      Photographer if identified: Rappoport Studios Inc.
    - Mitchell, Bertie (Box A-85, Folder 96)
    - Mitchell, Billy (Box A-85, Folder 97)
    - Mitchell, Blue (Box A-85, Folder 98)
    - Mitchell, Brian (Box A-85, Folder 99)
    - Mitchell, Carol (Box A-85, Folder 100)
      Photographer if identified: Irving Overby
    - Mitchell, Chad (Box A-85, Folder 101)
    - Mitchell, Charlene (Box A-85, Folder 102)
    - Mitchell, Charles (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-85, Folder 103)
    - Mitchell, Charles (Mrs.) (Box A-85, Folder 104)
    - Mitchell, Charles V. (Box A-85, Folder 105)
    - Mitchell, Clarence (Box A-85, Folder 106)
    - Mitchell, Clarence M. (Box A-85, Folder 107)
    - Mitchell, David (Box A-85, Folder 108)
    - Mitchell, David S. (Sgt.) (Box A-85, Folder 109)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, United Press International Photo
    - Mitchell, David W. (Box A-85, Folder 110)
    - Mitchell, Don (Box A-85, Folder 111)
    - Mitchell, Dorothy (Box A-85, Folder 112)
    - Mitchell, Dawn (Box A-85, Folder 113)
    - Mitchell, E. (Dr.) (Box A-85, Folder 114)
    - Mitchell, Edward James (Box A-85, Folder 115)
    - Mitchell, Ella (Box A-85, Folder 116)
    - Mitchell, Ellis (Box A-85, Folder 117)
    - Mitchell, Frank (Box A-85, Folder 118)
      Also two carbonscript leaves attached to each other by paperclip.
    - Mitchell, Freddie (Box A-85, Folder 119)
      Print is a postcard.
    - Mitchell, Gay (Box A-85, Folder 120)
    - Mitchell, Geneva (Box A-85, Folder 121)
    - Mitchell, George (Box A-85, Folder 122)
    - Mitchell, Glenford E. (Box A-85, Folder 123)
    - Mitchell, Gwen (Box A-85, Folder 124)
      Also one velox print with a caption stuck to the verso.
      Photographer if identified: Lionel Hinds, Randy Munkacsi
    - Mitchell, Harold (Box A-85, Folder 125)
    - Mitchell, Helen (Dr.) (Box A-85, Folder 126)
      Also one typescript leaf with a paperclip affixed to the corner.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, J. Connaughton, Spot News Agency
    - Mitchell, Helen (Dr.) (Box A-85, Folder 127)
      Photographer if identified: C. Brownie Harris
    - Mitchell, Henry H., Sr. (Box A-85, Folder 128)
    - Mitchell, Henry M. (Box A-85, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: Fr. D. Natale
    - Mitchell, Ivor D. (Box A-85, Folder 130)
    - Mitchell, Jack (Box A-85, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Rod Rogers Dance Co.
    - Mitchell, James (Box A-85, Folder 132)
    - Mitchell, James F. (Box A-85, Folder 133)
      Print has two staples through the border.
    - Mitchell, Jessie (Box A-85, Folder 134)
    - Mitchell, Joan (Box A-85, Folder 135)
    - Mitchell, John (Box A-85, Folder 136)
      Photographer if identified: Ed Entin
    - Mitchell, John N. (Atty. Gen.) (Box A-85, Folder 137)
      Two prints are attached to one carbonscript leaf and three typescript leaves (attached to each other by staple) by paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: USDA Photo
    - Mitchell, John W. (Box A-85, Folder 138)
    - Mitchell, Joseph R., Sr. (Dr.) (Box A-85, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: Polk's Studio
    - Mitchell, Ken (Box A-85, Folder 140)
    - Mitchell, Lamb (Box A-85, Folder 141)
    - Mitchell, Leona (Box A-85, Folder 142)
    - Mitchell, Leona (Box A-85, Folder 143)
      Photographer if identified: Christian Steiner
    - Mitchell, Lilly (Box A-85, Folder 144)
    - Mitchell, Lionel (Box A-85, Folder 145)
    - Mitchell, Lloyd (Box A-85, Folder 146)
      Print is cut from a larger image and affixed to paper backing with tape.
    - Mitchell, Lloyd (Box A-85, Folder 147)
    - Mitchell, Loften (Box A-85, Folder 148)
      Also four negative strips in glassine containing a total of twenty-four images. One print is attached to one ms. leaf and three typescript leaves (attached to each other by staple) attached by paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Aaron Smith Jr., James Gilbert, Ron Greene
    - Mitchell, Lonnie (Dr.) (Box A-85, Folder 149)
    - Mitchell, Lucias (Box A-85, Folder 150)
    - Mitchell, Margery H. (Box A-85, Folder 151)
    - Mitchell, Martha (Box A-85, Folder 152)
    - Mitchell, Martha M. (Box A-85, Folder 153)
    - Mitchell, Michael Bowen (Sen.) (Box A-85, Folder 154)
      Print has a typescript caption strip affixed to the recto with tape.
      Photographer if identified: I.H. Phillips
    - Mitchell, Millard (Box A-85, Folder 155)
    - Mitchell, Nonnie (Box A-85, Folder 156)
      Also one velox affixed to paper backing with tape.
    - Mitchell, Norm (Box A-85, Folder 157)
    - Mitchell, Ozie (Box A-85, Folder 158)
    - Mitchell, Parren (Box A-85, Folder 159)
      Also three velox prints. Two velox prints have a caption stuck to the recto. One velox is affixed to paper backing with tape and is torn. Also one carbonscript leaf. One print is a Polaroid.
      Photographer if identified: Morgan State College News Bureau, Marvin T. Jones
    - Mitchell, Pauline (Box A-85, Folder 160)
      Photographer if identified: Ricks
    - Mitchell, Pearlie B. (Box A-85, Folder 161)
    - Mitchell, Prince Phillip (Box A-85, Folder 162)
    - Mitchell, Ray (Box A-85, Folder 163)
    - Mitchell, Roderick B. (Box A-85, Folder 164)
    - Mitchell, Ron (Box A-85, Folder 165)
    - Mitchell, Ronald (Miss) (Box A-85, Folder 166)
      Photographer if identified: Photo by West
    - Mitchell, Roscoe E. (Box A-85, Folder 167)
    - Mitchell, Ruth (Box A-85, Folder 168)
    - Mitchell, Samuel S. (Box A-85, Folder 169)
    - Mitchell, Sandy (Box A-85, Folder 170)
    - Mitchell, Sara (Box A-85, Folder 171)
    - Mitchell, Scoey (Box A-85, Folder 172)
      Prints are attached to one typescript leaf by paperclip.
    - Mitchell, Taxi (Box A-85, Folder 173)
      Four prints are attached to each other by paperclip. Three of those prints are attached to each other by staple.
    - Mitchell, Ted (Box A-85, Folder 174)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Locall 1199
    - Mitchell, Theodore (Box A-85, Folder 175)
    - Mitchell, Timothy (Rev.) (Box A-85, Folder 176)
    - Mitchell, Timothy P. (Rev.) (Box A-85, Folder 177)
    - Mitchell, Tom (Box A-85, Folder 178)
    - Mitchell, Vernon (Box A-85, Folder 179)
      Print is attached to three typescript leaves by paperclip, two of which are attached to each other by staple.
      Photographer if identified: Information Office US Army Signal Center and School
    - Mitchell, Walter 33X (Box A-85, Folder 180)
    - Mitchell, William A. (Box A-85, Folder 181)
    - Mitchell, William L. (Rev. Dr.) (Box A-85, Folder 182)
      Photographer if identified: van Westrop Photo
    - Mitchell, William P. (Box A-85, Folder 183)
    - Mitchell, Wilis F. (Major) (Box A-85, Folder 184)
    - Mitchell-Lama Houses, Residents of (Box A-85, Folder 185)
    - Mitchelson, Lisa (Box A-85, Folder 186)
    - Mitchelson, Thomas P. (Capt.) (Box A-85, Folder 187)